Ignacio Ezequiel Iriondo

Buenos Aires City, Argentina Calasanz 227 2°B, ZIP CODE (1424) nachoiriondo90@gmail.com I +54 (011) 6114-6735



Professional Profile

Civil Engineer graduate from the School of Engineering - University of Buenos Aires. Analytical, with capacity for teamwork and very good management of interpersonal relationships. I feel very confident working in a team, and it gives me satisfaction when I help others solve their problems. Organized, responsible and always willing to learn

I have got experience in geosynthetics and geotechnical engineering, environmental and erosion control solutions.

As a civil inspector, I monitor different contractors' daily works on different underground constructions, making daily inspection visits, progress reports and quality supervision on site. Experience in open excavations, tunnelling excavations, reinforced concrete and steel structures.

Work Experience

Jun 2018 - Present **Buenos Aires Underground State-Owned Enterprise**

> Site Engineer - Civil Inspector: Reports and progress control, work schedules, technical documentation, structural analysis and verification,

plans control and review, construction supervision.

Civil Engineer professional Jun 2018 - Present

> Structural Analysis: Documentation, plans, calculation, analysis and materials' quantity of reinforced concrete structures, steel structures,

foundation structures, knowledge of ACI and CIRSOC code.

Feb 2016 - May 2018 **CORIPA S.A.**

> Technical-Commercial Engineer: Construction plans and calculation reports. Preparation of reports and technical proposals. Technical advice in coastal work, erosion control, environmental solutions, geosynthetics. Assistance in the design, calculation, specification and installation of the different products and technologies offered. Computation and budget.

Education

Mar 2010 - May2018 **Bachelor's Degree**

University of Buenos Aires - School of Engineering

Civil Engineer

Courses

- Postgraduate course Continuing Education: Project Management (100hs). UTN National Technological University – e-Learning Center
- Postgraduate course Continuing Education: Project Control (30hs). School of Engineering University of Buenos Aires – 2020
- Postgraduate course Continuing Education: Design and Construction of Tunnels and Underground Structures (32hs). School of Engineering – University of Buenos Aires – 2020

Languages

- Spanish Native
- **English** B2 Level (Preparing to take the IELTS exam: International English Language Test System)

Technical (IT) Skills

Graphics Autodesk AUTOCAD

Platforms
Microsoft Office, Microsoft Project, MathCAD Prime

BIM & 3D Modelling Autodesk REVIT, Sketchup

• Civil Engineering SAP2000, ETABS, ROBOT STRUCTURAL, CYPECAD, EXAMINE2D